<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<!-- ENGLISH -->
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
			<text>Commodore International
Personal computer
Fourth
1992
Floppy disk, IDE hard drive
Joystick, mouse, keyboard</text>
		</text>
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
			<text>The Amiga 1200 (A1200) released in 1992 is the third-generation computer from Commodore. It incorporates a processor 68020 2 times more powerful clocked at 14 MHz supported by an AGA graphic chipset, 2 MB of RAM as standard, and the sound always on 4-way stereo 8Bit. The normal mode display changes to 256 colors and 262,144 colors in HAM-8 mode from a palette of 16,777,216. Two types of games appear, those simply adapted to use the AGA like Chaos Engine, and those that will get 100% off like the cult Payback, Guardian, Banshee, Alien Breed 3D & Pinball Illusions.</text>
		</text>
		
		<!-- FRENCH -->
		<text name="sys_info" lang="fr" extra="true">
			<text>Commodore International
Ordinateur personnel
Quatrième
1992
Disquette, Disque dur IDE
Manette, souris, clavier</text>
		</text>
		<text name="sys_description" lang="fr" extra="true">
			<text>L'Amiga 1200 (A1200) sorti en 1992 est l'ordinateur de troisième génération de Commodore. Il incorpore un processeur 68020 2 fois plus puissant cadencé à 14 MHz épaulé d’un Chipset graphique AGA, 2 Mo de RAM en standard, et le son toujours sur 4 voies stéréo 8Bit. L'affichage en mode normal passe à 256 couleurs et à 262 144 couleurs en mode HAM-8 parmi une palette de 16 777 216. Apparaissent alors 2 types de jeux, ceux simplement adaptés pour utiliser l’AGA comme Chaos Engine, et ceux qui en tireront 100% parti comme les cultissimes Guardian, Banshee & Pinball Illusions.</text>
		</text>

		<!-- SPANISH -->
		<text name="sys_info" lang="sp" extra="true">
			<text>Commodore International
Ordenador personal
Cuarta
1992
Disquete, disco duro IDE
Joystick, ratón, teclado</text>
		</text>
		<text name="sys_description" lang="sp" extra="true">
			<text>El Amiga 1200 (A1200) lanzado en 1992 es la computadora de tercera generación de Commodore. Incorpora un procesador 68020 2 veces más potente con una velocidad de reloj de 14 MHz compatible con un chipset gráfico AGA, 2 MB de RAM de serie y el sonido siempre en 8 bits estéreo de 4 vías. La pantalla del modo normal cambia a 256 colores y 262,144 colores en el modo HAM-8 desde una paleta de 16,777,216. Aparecen dos tipos de juegos, aquellos simplemente adaptados para usar el AGA como Chaos Engine, y aquellos que obtendrán un 100% de descuento como las culto Payback. Guardian, Banshee, Alien Breed 3D y Pinball Illusions.</text>
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>