<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Commodore
Home video game console
Fifth
1993
CD-Rom
7 buttons Gamepad, mouse</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Commodore
Console de salon
Cinquième
1993
CD-Rom
Manette 7 boutons, souris</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Commodore
Consola de videojuegos salón
Quinta
1993
CD-Rom
Gamepad 7 botones, ratón</text>

		</text>
		
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >The Amiga CD32 is a fifth generation video game console marketed by Commodore in September 1993. It’s a console whose architecture is similar to the Amiga 1200 with a CD-ROM drive. It is the first 32-bit to be released in the West, FM Towns Marty having preceded it in Japan. Like the 3DO or Jaguar, marketed at the same time, the CD32 failed to break into the market in the face of PSX and Saturn. Due to its technical limitations, its bitmap display mode greatly limits it in the display of textured 3D games then in fashion. Part of the CDTV catalog is compatible with the console.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Sortie en 1993 l’Amiga CD32 est une console de cinquième génération. Son architecture est similaire à l’Amiga 1200 avec l’ajout d’une puce Akiko pour le mode bitplan (C2P) et le lecteur de CD-Rom. Première 32-bit à voir le jour en occident, elle est précédée au Japon par la FM Towns Marty. Comme la 3DO ou la Jaguar, commercialisées à la même période, la CD32 n'est pas parvenue à percer sur le marché face à la PSX et la Saturn. Faute à ses limitations techniques, ses limitations dans l'affichage des jeux en 3D texturée alors à la mode. Une partie du catalogue CDTV est compatible avec la console.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">La Amiga CD32 es una consola de videojuegos de quinta generación comercializada por Commodore en septiembre de 1993. Es una consola cuya arquitectura es similar a la Amiga 1200 con una unidad de CD-ROM. Es el primer disco de 32 bits que se lanzará en Occidente, ya que FM Towns Marty lo precedió en Japón. Al igual que el 3DO o el Jaguar, comercializado al mismo tiempo, el CD32 no logró ingresar al mercado frente a PSX y Saturn. Debido a sus limitaciones técnicas, su modo de visualización de mapa de bits lo limita enormemente en la visualización de juegos 3D texturizados, entonces de moda.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>