<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Commodore International
Personal computer
Fourth
1987
Floppy disk, IDE hard drive
Joystick, mouse, keyboard</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Commodore International
Ordinateur personnel
Quatrième
1987
Disquette, Disque dur IDE
Manette, souris, clavier</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Commodore International
Ordenador personal
Cuarta
1987
Disquete, disco duro IDE
Joystick, ratón, teclado</text>

		</text>
		
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >The Amiga 500 (A500) is Commodore's first 16/32-bit entry-level computer. Released in 1987, it is in direct competition with the Atari 520 ST. The Amiga 500 uses a Motorola 68000 processor clocked at 7 MHz, 512 KB of RAM as standard, a Denise chip for display and a Paula chip to manage the sound on 4 channels (Chris Hülsbeck will manage to mount up to 8) . It can originate display in 320 × 256 pixels and 32 colors or 640 × 512 pixels and 16 colors, but in late 1989 with special modes they go up to 128 colors on the screen. Cult games will then see the day as Shadow of the Beast.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">L'Amiga 500 (A500) est le premier ordinateur 16/32 bits d’entrée de gamme Commodore. Sorti en 1987, il est en concurrence directe avec l'Atari 520 ST. L'Amiga 500 utilise un processeur Motorola 68000 cadencé à 7 MHz, 512 Ko de RAM en standard, une puce Denise pour l’affichage et une puce Paula pour gérer le son sur 4 voies (Chris Hülsbeck arrivera à monter jusqu’à 8). Il peut d’origine afficher en 320×256 pixels et 32 couleurs ou  640×512 pixels et 16 couleurs, mais fin 1989 avec les modes spéciaux il mont à 128 couleurs à l'écran. Des jeux cultes verront alors le jour comme Shadow of the Beast.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">El Amiga 500 (A500) es la primera computadora de nivel básico de 16/32 bits de Commodore. Lanzado en 1987, compite directamente con el Atari 520 ST. El Amiga 500 utiliza un procesador Motorola 68000 con velocidad de reloj de 7 MHz, 512 KB de RAM como estándar, un chip Denise para visualización y un chip Paula para administrar el sonido en 4 canales (Chris Hülsbeck logrará montar hasta 8). Puede originar la visualización en 320 × 256 píxeles y 32 colores o 640 × 512 píxeles y 16 colores, pero a fines de 1989 con modos especiales suben hasta 128 colores en la pantalla.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>