<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Apple
Personal computer
First
1977
Cassette tape, 5¼ floppy disk
Joystick, keyboard</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Apple
Ordinateur personnel
Première
1977
Cassette, disquette 5¼
Joystick, clavier</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Apple
Ordenador personal
Primero
1977
Casete , Disquete 5¼
Joystick, Teclado</text>

		</text>
		
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >The Apple II is one of the world's first large-scale personal computers. Designed by Steve Wozniak and marketed on June 10, 1977 by Apple, it began its career with passionate individuals. The Apple II uses an 8-bit architecture, 4 KB of RAM, a cassette player and allows a display in 280x192 in 6 colors in composite video output. The Apple IIe Enhanced released in 1984 has 128k of RAM. Its display evolves to reach 560x192 in monochrome, 280x192 in 6 colors and 140x192 in 16 colors. Apple will stop production of its Apple II line in 1993.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">L'Apple II est l'un des premiers ordinateurs personnels au monde fabriqué à grande échelle. Conçu par Steve Wozniak et commercialisé le 10 juin 1977 par Apple, il commence sa carrière auprès des particuliers passionnés. L'Apple II utilise une architecture 8 bits, 4ko de RAM, un lecteur de cassete et permet un affichage en 280x192 en 6 couleurs en sortie vidéo composite. L'Apple IIe Enhanced (Amélioré) sorti en 1984 dispose de 128k de RAM. Son affichage évolue pour atteindre du 560x192 en monochrome, 280x192 en 6 couleurs et 140x192 en 16 couleurs.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">La Apple II es una de las primeras computadoras personales a gran escala del mundo. Diseñado por Steve Wozniak y comercializado el 10 de junio de 1977 por Apple, comenzó su carrera con personas apasionadas. El Apple II utiliza una arquitectura de 8 bits, 4 KB de RAM, un reproductor de cassette y permite una pantalla de 280x192 en 6 colores en salida de video compuesto. El Apple IIe Enhanced lanzado en 1984 tiene 128k de RAM. Su pantalla evoluciona para alcanzar 560x192 en monocromo, 280x192 en 6 colores y 140x192 en 16 colores.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>