<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Atari
Home video game console
Fifth
1993
Cartridge, CD-Rom
Joystick</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Atari
Console de salon
Cinquième
1993
Cartouche, CD-Rom
Manette de jeu</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Atari
Videoconsola sobremesa
Quinta
1993
Cartucho, CD-Rom
Joystick</text>

		</text>
		
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >The Jaguar is a living room console with cartridges (CD player sold separately) released in 1993 and having a limited toy library because it has not been very successful. It was in its time the only 64-bit console, the PlayStation and Saturn being 32-bit, causing controversy. The two 64-bit processors of the Jaguar are nothing more than graphics accelerators, its graphics processor is a 32-bit and its CPU is a 16-bit at 13 MHz. With its 2 MB of RAM it displays a resolution of 720x526 pixels in 16 million colors. One of his cult games will be 'Alien vs. Predator'.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">La Jaguar est une console de salon à cartouches (lecteur CD vendu séparément) sortie en1993 et disposant d'une ludothèque limitée car elle n'a pas connu un grand succès. Elle est en son temps la seule console 64 bits, la PlayStation et la Saturn étant des 32 bits, causant une controverse. Les deux processeurs 64 bits de la Jaguar ne sont rien de plus que des accélérateurs graphiques, son processeur graphique est un 32 bits et son CPU un 16 bits à 13 Mhz. Avec ses 2 Mo de RAM elle affiche une résolution de 720x526 pixels en 16 millions de couleurs. L’un de ses jeux culte sera "Alien vs. Predator".</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">El Jaguar es una consola de sala de estar con cartuchos (el reproductor de CD se vende por separado) lanzado en 1993 y tiene una biblioteca de juguetes limitada porque no ha tenido mucho éxito. Fue en su momento la única consola de 64 bits, PlayStation y Saturn con 32 bits, lo que causó controversia. Los dos procesadores de 64 bits del Jaguar no son más que aceleradores gráficos, su procesador gráfico es de 32 bits y su CPU es de 16 bits a 13 MHz. Con sus 2 MB de RAM, muestra una resolución de 720x526 píxeles en 16 millones de colores. Uno de sus juegos de culto será 'Alien vs. Predator'.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>