<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Commodore International
Personal computer
Third
1984
Cassette tape, floppy disk
Joystick, keyboard</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Commodore International
Ordinateur personnel
Troisième
1984
Cartouches, cassette
Joystick, clavier</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Commodore International
Ordenador personal
Tercero
1984
Casete, disquete
Joystick 1 botone, teclado</text>

		</text>

		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >Released in 1984 to replace the VIC-20, the Commodore C116, C16 and Plus / 4 range targeted the entry-level market. A MOS7501 or 8501 processor succeeds the 6502 and is 75% faster. However only one TED co-processor is included for audio and video. Also unlike the C64, no hardware acceleration exists on these machines. The Plus / 4 has 32k of RAM and integrates four office applications into it. This project was a commercial failure in the USA and stopped in 1985 even if copies were sold in Europe and especially in the east, behind the iron curtain.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Sortie en 1984 pour remplacer le VIC-20, la gamme Commodore C116, C16 et Plus/4 visait le marché d'entrée de gammme. Un processeur MOS7501 ou 8501 succéde au 6502 et est 75% plus rapide. Cependant un seul co-processeur TED est inclus pour le son et la video. Aussi contrairement au C64, aucune accélération matérielle n'existe sur ces machines. Le Plus/4 a 32k de RAM et y intègre quatre applications bureautiques. Ce projet fut un échec commercial aux USA et s'arrêta en 1985 même si des exemplaires se sont vendus en Europe et surtout à l'est, derrière le rideau de fer.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Lanzado en 1984 para reemplazar el VIC-20, la gama Commodore C116, C16 y Plus / 4 se dirigió al mercado de nivel de entrada. Un procesador MOS7501 o 8501 sucede al 6502 y es un 75% más rápido. Sin embargo, solo se incluye un coprocesador TED para audio y video. Además, a diferencia del C64, no existe aceleración de hardware en estas máquinas. El Plus / 4 tiene 32k de RAM e integra cuatro aplicaciones de oficina. Este proyecto fue un fracaso comercial en los EE. UU. Y se detuvo en 1985, incluso si se vendieron copias en Europa y especialmente en el este, detrás de la cortina de hierro.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>