<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Commodore
Personal computer
Third
1982
Cartridge, digital tape, floppy
Joystick, keyboard, mouse</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Commodore
Ordinateur personnel
Troisième
1982
Cartouche, casette, disquette
Joystick, clavier, souris</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Commodore
Ordenador personal
Tercero
1982
Cartucho, cinta digital, disque.
Joypad, teclado, ratón</text>

		</text>

		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >The Commodore 64 is a personal computer designed by the firm of Jack Tramiel in 1982. It remains the best-selling model of its decade with 13 million copies sold worldwide. It uses an 8-bit 6510 microprocessor and has 64 kilobytes of RAM. Its graphics chip, VIC-II, provides 16 colors and hardware scrolling and sprite capabilities. The sound chip, SID, has three voices, several waveforms, sound modulations and filtering capabilities. It is very advanced for its time. Its designer, Bob Yannes, will be the co-founder of the synthesizer company Ensoniq.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Le Commodore 64 est un ordinateur personnel conçu par la firme de Jack Tramiel en 1982. Il reste le modèle le plus vendu de sa décénnie avec 13 millions d'exemplaires écoulés dans le monde. Il utilise un microprocesseur 8-bits 6510 et dispose de 64 ko de mémoire vive. Sa puce graphique, VIC-II, fournit 16 couleurs et des capacités de scrolling et sprites hardware. La puce sonore, SID, a trois voix, plusieurs formes d'ondes, modulations sonores et capacités de filtrage. Elle est très avancée pour son époque. Son concepteur, Bob Yannes, sera le cofondateur de la société de synthétiseur Ensoniq.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">El Commodore 64 es una computadora personal diseñada por la firma de Jack Tramiel en 1982. Sigue siendo el modelo más vendido de su década con 13 millones de copias vendidas en todo el mundo. Utiliza un microprocesador 6510 de 8 bits y tiene 64 ko de RAM. Su chip gráfico, VIC-II, proporciona 16 colores y capacidades de desplazamiento de hardware y sprite. El chip de sonido, SID, tiene tres voces, varias formas de onda, modulaciones de sonido y capacidades de filtrado. Está muy avanzado para su tiempo. Su diseñador, B. Yannes, será el cofundador de la compañía de sintetizadores Ensoniq.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>