<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Pixel
Action, Patform
Second
2005
Cartridge
Joypad</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Pixel
Action, Plateforme
Deuxième
2005
Cartouche
Joypad</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Pixel
Acción, Plataforma
Todas
2005
Ejecutable
Joypad</text>

		</text>

		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >Cave Story is an action-adventure and horizontal scrolling platform game in the tradition of the famous Wonderboy or Castlevania. You control a small character who has decided to help creatures resembling rabbits, the Mimigas and must find your way in the gigantic labyrinth of underground passages of a flying island. You can collect multiple weapons, change them at will, collect experience points by killing enemies and thus raise them to level 3. But taking damage causes experience points, or even levels, to be lost.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Cave Story est un jeu d'action-aventure et de plateforme à scrolling horizontal dans la lignée des célèbres Wonderboy ou Castlevania. Vous contrôlez un petit personnage qui a décidé d'aider des créatures ressemblant à des lapins, les Mimigas et devez trouver votre route dans le gigantesque labyrinthe de souterrains d'une île volante. Vous pouvez collecter plusieurs armes, en changer à volonté, ramasser des points d’expérience en tuant les ennemis et ainsi les monter jusqu’au niveau 3. Mais prendre des dégâts fait perdre des points d'expérience, voire des niveaux, aux armes.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Cave Story es un juego de plataformas de acción, aventura y desplazamiento horizontal en la tradición del famoso Wonderboy o Castlevania. Controlas a un pequeño personaje que ha decidido ayudar a las criaturas que se parecen a los conejos, los Mimigas, y debes encontrar tu camino en el gigantesco laberinto de pasajes subterráneos de una isla voladora. Puedes recoger varias armas, cambiarlas a voluntad, acumular puntos de experiencia matando enemigos y así elevarlos al nivel 3. Pero recibir daño hace que se pierdan puntos de experiencia, o incluso niveles.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>