<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Coleco Industries
Home video game console
Second
1982
Cartridge
Analog stick & 14 buttons</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Coleco Industies
Console de salon
Deuxième
1982
Cartouche
Stick analogique & 14 boutons</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Coleco Industries
Videoconsola sobremesa
Segundo
1982
Cartucho
Stick analógico y 14 botones</text>

		</text>

		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >The Colecovision is a second generation video game console marketed by Coleco (Connecticut Leather Company) and released in August 1982. Equipped with a 3.58 Mhz processor, 1 kb of RAM, 3 tone and 1 noise generators, it displays a Resolution of 256x192 pixels and 32 sprites in 16 colors. This allows him to offer graphics similar to arcade games of the time. About 170 titles were released during his lifetime, and he still continues to leave Homebrew in 2020. Coleco has also marketed a module that makes the console compatible with the Atari 2600.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">La Colecovision est une console de jeu vidéo de seconde génération commercialisée par Coleco (Connecticut Leather Company) et sortie en août 1982. Equipée d’un processeur 3.58 Mhz, 1 ko de RAM, 3 générateurs de ton et 1 de bruit, elle affiche une résolution de 256x192 pixels et 32 sprites en 16 couleurs. Celà lui permet de proposer des graphismes similaires aux jeux d'arcade de l'époque. Environ 170 titres sont sortis pendant toute sa vie, et il continue encore de sortir de Homebrew en 2020. Coleco a aussi commercialisé un module qui rend la console compatible avec l'Atari 2600.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">La Colecovision es una consola de videojuegos de segunda generación comercializada por Coleco (Connecticut Leather Company) y lanzada en agosto de 1982. Equipada con un procesador de 3.58 Mhz, 1 kb de RAM, 3 tonos y 1 generador de ruido, muestra un Resolución de 256x192 píxeles y 32 sprites en 16 colores. Esto le permite ofrecer gráficos similares a los juegos de arcade de la época. Se lanzaron alrededor de 170 títulos durante su vida, y aún continúa dejando Homebrew en 2020. Coleco también ha comercializado un módulo que hace que la consola sea compatible con el Atari 2600.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>