<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Microsoft & Intel, AMD
Personnal computer
Third / Fourth
1982
Floppy disk 5¼ 3½, hard disk
Joystick, keyboard, mouse</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Microsoft & Intel, AMD
Ordinateur personnel
Troisième / Quatrième
1982
Disquette 5¼ & 3½, disque dur
Joystick, clavier, souris</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Microsoft & Intel, AMD
Ordenador personal
Tercera / Cuarta
1982
Disquete 5¼ 3½, disco duro
Joystick, teclado, ratón</text>

		</text>

		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >We call DOS (disk operating system) the PC operating system equipped by default with a command line interface developed by Microsoft in 1981. With the 6 to 20 MHz processor from Intel 80286 launched in 1982 followed by the i386 in 12 At 40 MHz from 1985, this OS will be used in many personal computers. This power will be exploited to create the first micro games in CGA 320x200 4 colors then from 1984 in EGA 640x350 16 colors. Starting from Rogue or Troll’s Tale, ending with the first Leisure Suit Larry then Battle Chess and King’s Quest 4 in 1988.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">On appelle DOS (disk operating system) le système d'exploitation PC équipé par défaut d'une interface en ligne de commande développé par Microsoft en 1981. Avec le processeur 6 à 20 MHz d’Intel 80286 lancé en 1982 suivi du i386 en 12 à 40 MHz de 1985, cet OS sera utilisé dans de nombreux ordinateurs personnels. Cette puissance sera exploitée pour créer les premiers jeux micro en CGA 320x200 4 couleurs puis à partir de 1984 en EGA 640x350 16 couleurs. En partant de Rogue ou Troll’s Tale, pour terminer par le premier Leisure Suit Larry puis Battle Chess et King’s Quest 4 en 1988.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Llamamos DOS (sistema operativo de disco) al sistema operativo de PC equipado por defecto con una interfaz de línea de comandos desarrollada por Microsoft en 1981. Con el procesador de 6 a 20 MHz de Intel 80286 lanzado en 1982 seguido por el i386 en 12 A 40 MHz desde 1985, este sistema operativo se utilizará en muchas computadoras personales. Esta potencia se explotará para crear los primeros microjuegos en CGA 320x200 4 colores y luego desde 1984 en EGA 640x350 16 colores. Comenzando desde Rogue o Troll’s Tale, terminando con el primer Leisure Suit Larry y luego Battle Chess.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>