<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Nintendo
Handheld game console
Sixth
2001
Cartridge GBA, GB, GBC
4 buttons Joypad</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Nintendo
Console portable
Sixième
2001
Cartouches GBA, GB, GBC
Manette 4 boutons</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Nintendo
Consola portátil
Sexto
2001
Cartuchos GBA, GB, GBC
Controlador de 4 botones</text>

		</text>
		
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >The Game Boy Advance is a portable console created by Nintendo in 2001. It has a color screen and 32-bit processor, but no 3D instructions. It is the most powerful portable console of the moment. Equipped with a 16 Mhz processor, an 8 Mhz GPU and 380 KB of RAM it displays a resolution of 240x160 in 511 colors. In 2003, Nintendo launched the GBA SP, with improvements such as a backlit screen, a reduced size, as well as a rechargeable lithium-ion battery. Finally in 2005, Nintendo released the Game Boy Micro, the latest version of its laptop.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">La Game Boy Advance est une console portable créée par Nintendo en 2001. Elle dispose d'un écran couleur et d'un processeur 32 bits, mais pas d’instructions 3D. Elle est la console portable la plus performante du moment. Équipée d’un processeur 16 Mhz, un GPU 8 Mhz et 380 Ko de RAM elle affiche une résolution de 240x160 en 511 couleurs. En 2003, Nintendo lance la GBA SP, disposant d'améliorations telles qu'un écran rétro-éclairé, une taille réduite, ainsi qu'une batterie lithium-ion rechargeable. Enfin en 2005, Nintendo sort la Game Boy Micro, dernière déclinaison de sa portable.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Game Boy Advance es una consola portátil creada por Nintendo en 2001. Tiene una pantalla a color y un procesador de 32 bits, pero no tiene instrucciones en 3D. Es la consola portátil más potente del momento. Equipado con un procesador de 16 Mhz, una GPU de 8 Mhz y 380 KB de RAM, muestra una resolución de 240x160 en 511 colores. En 2003, Nintendo lanzó el GBA SP, con mejoras tales como una pantalla retroiluminada, un tamaño reducido, así como una batería recargable de iones de litio. Finalmente, en 2005, Nintendo lanzó Game Boy Micro, la última versión de su computadora portátil.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>