<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Nintendo
Home video game console
Sixth
2001
Mini Disc 1.5 Go
Controller, Wavebird</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Nintendo
Console de salon
Sixième
2001
Mini Disc 1.5 Go
Manette, Wavebird</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Nintendo
Videoconsola sobremesa
Sexto
2001
Mini Disc 1.5 Go
Joystick, Wavebird</text>

		</text>
		
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >Released in 2001, the GC did not meet the success of its elders, facing the PS2, XBox and Dreamcast. A cable however made it possible to use GBA as a controller with a remote screen for Zelda Four Swords Adv. and in 2002 released the Wavebird, the first wireless controller by radio wave. Equipped with a processor at 486 Mhz, an ATI graphics chip at 162 Mhz and 40 MB of RAM it can calculate 15 million polygons. It displays 640×480 60 Hz or 768x576 50 Hz and offers sound in Dolby Pro Logic 2. It presents a catalog of 644 games including games like Resident Evil 4 and Viewtiful Joe.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Sortie en 2001, la GC ne rencontra pas le succès de ses ainées, face aux PS2, XBox et Dreamcast. Un câble permettait pourtant d'utiliser des GBA comme manette avec écran déporté pour Zelda Four Swords Adv. et en 2002 sorti la Wavebird, première manette sans fil par onde radio. Dotée d'un processeur à 486 Mhz, une puce graphique ATI à 162 Mhz et 40 Mo de RAM elle peut calculer 15 millions de polygones. Elle affiche du 640×480 60 Hz ou du 768x576 50 Hz et propose un son en Dolby Pro Logic 2. Elle présente un catalogue de 644 jeux dont Resident Evil 4, Pikmin, Ikagura et Viewtiful Joe.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Lanzado en 2001, el GC no alcanzó el éxito de sus mayores, frente a PS2, XBox y Dreamcast. Sin embargo, un cable permitió utilizar GBA como controlador con una pantalla remota para Zelda Four Swords Adv. y en 2002 lanzó el Wavebird, el primer controlador inalámbrico por onda de radio. Equipado con un procesador a 486 Mhz, un chip gráfico ATI a 162 Mhz y 40 MB de RAM, puede calcular 15 millones de polígonos. Muestra 640×480 60 Hz o 768x576 50 Hz y ofrece sonido en Dolby Pro Logic 2. Presenta un catálogo de 644 juegos que incluye juegos como Resident Evil 4 y Viewtiful Joe.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>