<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Sega
Home video game console
Fourth
1988
Cartridge
Gamepad 3 or 6 buttons</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Sega
Console de salon
Quatrième
1988
Cartouche
Manette 3 ou 6 boutons</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Sega
Videoconsola sobremesa
Cuarto
1988
Cartucho
Joystick de 3 o 6 botones</text>

		</text>
		
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >Released in 1988, the Megadrive or Genesis in America, is the new Sega console based on the architecture of their Arcade System 16. Taking short Nintendo 16-bit market, Sega manages to position it in the United States and Europe, sweeping the way the PC Engine. It has a 7.6 MHz processor, 74 KB of RAM, a 320x224 display and 256x224 pixels in 64 colors among 512 and FM stereo sound. In 1991 the mascot of the brand Sonic the Hedgehog is released, followed by two excellent suites. But the Megadrive is also Disney Aladdin, EA sports games and the uncensored version of Mortal Kombat!</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Sortie en 1988, la Megadrive ou Genesis en Amérique, est la nouvelle console de Sega basé sur l’architecture de leur Système 16 arcade. Prenant de court Nintendo sur le marché des 16-bit, Sega parvient à la positionner aux États-Unis et en Europe, balayant au passage la PC Engine. Elle dispose d’un processeur 7.6 Mhz, 74 Ko de RAM, un affichage 320x224 et 256x224 pixels en 64 couleurs parmi 512 et d’un son FM stéréo. En 1991 sort Sonic la mascotte de la marque, suivi par 2 excellentes suites. Mais la MD c’est aussi Aladdin, les jeux de sport EA et la version non censuré de Mortal Kombat!</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Lanzado en 1988, Megadrive o Genesis in America, es la nueva consola Sega basada en la arquitectura de su arcade System 16. Al superar a Nintendo en el mercado de 16 bits, Sega logra posicionarlo en los Estados Unidos y Europa, barriendo el motor de PC en el proceso. Tiene un procesador de 7.6 Mhz, 74 KB de RAM, una pantalla de 320x224 y 256x224 píxeles en 64 colores entre 512 y sonido estéreo FM. En 1991, se lanzó Sonic, la mascota de la marca, seguida de 2 excelentes suites. ¡Pero MD también es Aladdin, los juegos deportivos de EA y la versión sin censura de Mortal Kombat!</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>