<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Microsoft & Sony, Pioneer
Personnal computer
Third
1983
Cartridge, floppy & tape disk
Joystick, mouse, keyboard</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Microsoft & Sony, Pioneer
Ordinateur personnel
Troisième
1983
Cartouche, disquette, cassette
Manette, souris, clavier</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Microsoft & Sony, Pioneer
Ordenator personal
Tercera
1983
Cartucho, disquete, casete
Joystick, ratón, teclado</text>

		</text>

		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >MSX is a standard of microcomputers with domestic vocation of Japanese origin. It dates from the 1980s so that computers produced by various manufacturers were compatible with each other thanks to Microsoft's MSX-DOS 1. MSX stands for Machines with Software eXchangeability, but it is often interpreted as MicroSoft eXtension. The MSX displayed graphics in 256 × 192 pixels with 16 colors and will see the first generation of games converted from the arcade as well as unique pearls such as Penguin Adventure, Exa Inova, Crusader, α-roid, Gall Force.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">MSX est un standard de micro-ordinateurs à vocation domestique d’origine japonaise. Il date des années 1980 pour que les ordinateurs produits par divers fabricants soient compatibles entre eux grâce au MSX-DOS 1 de Microsoft. Le sigle MSX signifie Machines with Software eXchangeability, mais il est souvent interprété comme MicroSoft eXtension. Le MSX affichait des graphismes en 256×192 pixels avec 16 couleurs et verra la première génération de jeux convertis de l’arcade ainsi que des perles uniques telles Penguin Adventure, Exa Inova, Crusader, α-roid, Gall Force.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">MSX es un estándar de microcomputadoras con vocación doméstica de origen japonés. Data de la década de 1980, por lo que las computadoras producidas por varios fabricantes eran compatibles entre sí gracias al MSX-DOS 1 de Microsoft. MSX significa Máquinas con intercambiabilidad de software, pero a menudo se interpreta como MicroSoft eXtension. El MSX mostró gráficos en 256 × 192 píxeles con 16 colores y verá la primera generación de juegos convertidos desde el arcade, así como perlas únicas como Penguin Adventure, Exa Inova, Crusader, α-roid, Gall Force.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>