<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Commodore International
Personal computer
First
1977
Cassette, floppy, hard disk
Keyboard</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Commodore International
Ordinateur personnel
Première
1977
Cassette, disquette, Ddur
Clavier</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Commodore International
Ordenador personal
Primero
1977
Casete, disquete, disco duro
Teclado</text>

		</text>

		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >Commodore launched in 1977 an integrated machine for personal use, under the name of Commodore PET 2001. This precursor computer is part of the famous '1977 Trinity' with the Apple II and the Tandy TRS-80. This Personal Electronic Transactor (or PET) was designed by Chuck Peddle as a monobloc box, incorporating keyboard, reduced screen and cassette player, the first microcomputer ready to operate as soon as it is connected. Current competitors like the Apple II and the TRS-80 required an external tape recorder.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Commodore lança en 1977 une machine intégrée à usage personnel, sous la dénomination de Commodore PET 2001. Cet ordinateur précurseur fait parti de la célèbre "Trinité de 1977" avec l'Apple II et le Tandy TRS-80. Ce Personal Electronic Transactor (ou PET) était conçu par Chuck Peddle comme un boîtier monobloc, incorporant clavier, écran de taille réduite et lecteur de cassettes, le premier micro-ordinateur prêt à fonctionner dès son branchement. Les concurrents du moment comme l'Apple II et le TRS-80 nécessitaient un magnétophone externe.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Commodore lanzó en 1977 una máquina integrada para uso personal, bajo el nombre de Commodore PET 2001. Esta computadora precursora es parte de la famosa 'Trinidad de 1977' con el Apple II y el Tandy TRS-80. Este Transactor electrónico personal (o PET) fue diseñado por Chuck Peddle como un estuche monobloque, que incorpora teclado, pantalla reducida y reproductor de cassette, el primer microordenador listo para funcionar tan pronto como se conecta. Los competidores actuales como el Apple II y el TRS-80 requerían una grabadora de cinta externa.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>