<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>Multiple
2D/3D Game Collection
All
1980 / 20xx
All supports 
Gamepad, Keyboard</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Multiple
Collection de jeu 2D/3D
Toutes
1980 / 20xx
Tous les supports
Manette, Clavier</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Multiples
Colección de Juegos 2D/3D
Toudas
1980 / 20xx
Todos los apoyos
Joypad, Teclado</text>

		</text>
		
		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >The pinball machine has its origins in the 18th century. Its ancestor is Bagatelle, an old game table invented in France. In 1930, with the invention of the coin mechanism, the pinball machine took on a new dimension. It becomes lucrative and arouses new interest. Between 1950 and 1970, the game knew a splendid period, it developed in the United States then exported to Europe and the rest of the world. In the 1980s, the pinball machine lost market share to the video game on which it was adapted. Nowadays, physical play is mainly carried by a clientele of nostalgic and new collectors.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Le flipper trouve ses origines au 18ème siècle. Il aurait pour ancêtre la Bagatelle, une ancienne table de jeu inventée en France. En 1930, avec l'invention du monnayeur, le flipper prend une nouvelle dimension. Il devient lucratif et suscite de nouveaux l’intérêt. Entre 1950 et 1970, le jeu connaît un période faste, il se développe aux États-unis puis s'exporte en Europe et dans le reste du monde. Dans les années 1980, le flipper perd des parts de marché au profit du jeu vidéo sur lequel il est adapté. De nos jours, le jeu physique est essentiellement porté par une clientèle de collectionneurs nostalgiques.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">La máquina de pinball tiene sus orígenes en el siglo XVIII. Su antepasado es Bagatelle, una vieja mesa de juego inventada en Francia. En 1930, con la invención del mecanismo de monedas, la máquina de pinball adquirió una nueva dimensión. Se vuelve lucrativo y despierta nuevo interés. Entre 1950 y 1970, el juego conoció un período espléndido, se desarrolló en los Estados Unidos y luego se exportó a Europa y al resto del mundo. En la década de 1980, la máquina de pinball perdió participación de mercado en el videojuego en el que se adaptó. El juego es llevado principalmente por una clientela de coleccionistas nostálgicos.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>