<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
	
		<text name="sys_info" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text>From id Software engine
3D game engine
0.61+
2009
PAK files
Joystick, keyboard, mouse</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">From id Software engine
Moteur de jeu 3D
0.61+
2009
Fichiers PAK
Manette de jeu, clavier, souris</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Desde el motor del software id
Motor de juego 3D
0.61+
2009
Archivos PAK
Joystick, teclado, mouse</text>

		</text>

		<text name="sys_description" extra="true">
		
<!-- ENGLISH -->
<text          >Quake is a series of first-person shooters developed by Id Software to succeed its Doom series. First FPS in true polygonal 3D, it was a real revolution. There are 4 games: Quake, Quake II, Quake III Arena and Quake 4. TyrQuake is an optimized version of the original Quake engine, the engine source code having been released under GPLv2 license on December 21, 1999. This allowed without modifying the Original gaming experience, to make various improvements such as better OpenGL support, improved lighting, more detailed maps, etc.</text>
<!-- FRENCH -->
<text lang="fr">Quake est une série de jeux de tir à la première personne développée par Id Software pour succéder à sa série Doom. Premier FPS en véritable 3D polygonale, il fut une véritable révolution. Il y a 4 jeux : Quake, Quake II, Quake III Arena et Quake 4. TyrQuake est une version optimisée du moteur Quake original, le code source du moteur ayant été publié sous licence GPLv2 le 21 décembre 1999. Cela a permis sans modifier l’expérience de jeu originale, d'apporter diverses améliorations comme un meilleur support OpenGL, une amélioration des éclairages, des cartes plus détaillées, etc.</text>
<!-- SPANISH -->
<text lang="sp">Quake es una serie de juegos de disparos en primera persona desarrollados por Id Software para tener éxito en su serie Doom. Primer FPS en 3D poligonal verdadero, fue una verdadera revolución. Hay 4 juegos: Quake, Quake II, Quake III Arena y Quake 4. TyrQuake es una versión optimizada del motor Quake original, el código fuente del motor se lanzó bajo licencia GPLv2 el 21 de diciembre de 1999. Esto permitió sin modificar el Experiencia de juego original, para realizar varias mejoras, como un mejor soporte OpenGL, iluminación mejorada, mapas más detallados, etc.</text>
			
		</text>
		
	</view>

</theme>